Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Chicago Office. Information Center Records, 1901-2005 and undated RL.11121
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- 2018 Additions, 1901-2006 and undated; 1
  - Audiovisual Materials, 1974-2005 and undated; 12
    - JWT World Partners Council "The Big Picture" issue 2, 1995 (Box AV3, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-048)
    - JWTV Asia Pacific Round Up "In Rome" 34:00, 1995 (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-049)
    - Kellogg's Rome presentation, 1995 (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-050)
    - The Kid Conundrum: How Do You Connect? Creative reel presented to Oscar Mayer, 2001 (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-051)
      Includes Blockbuster, Gatorade, McDonald's, Kellogg, Macromedia.com, Burger King, Wheaties, Barbie, Adidas, ONDCP, Pac Man, Gap, Dairylea, Hostess, Playland, Power Rangers, Domino, Budweiser, Pepsi, Taco Bell, Snickers
    - Kraft Advertising Review: Health and Wellness Video, 2003 (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-052)
    - Kraft: Breakstone Cottage Doubles, 2001 (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-053)
    - Kraft: Cheez Whiz, 2001 (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-054)
    - Kraft: Miracle Whip sales video, 2002 (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-055)
    - Kraft: Miracle Whip sales video, 2003 (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-056)
    - Kraft: Oscar Mayer "So Much Love", 2003 (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-057)
    - Kraft: Philadelphia agency versions, 2002 (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-058)
    - Kraft: Philadelphia Livomatics, 2002 (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-059)
    - Kraft: Philly on Toast, 1996 (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-060)
    - Kraft: Singles "Flying Carpet" animatic, 1994 (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-061)
    - Kraft: Teaching American Women How to Cook 4:38, 2001 (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-062)
    - Kraft: Teaching American Women How to Cook 4:38, 2001 (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-063)
    - Leo Burnett Creative Exchange: Cannes Lions winners reel 1 of 2, 1999 (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-064)
    - Leo Burnett Creative Exchange: Cannes Lions winners reel 2 of 2, 1999 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-065)
    - Lucy's Birthday Marathon, WFLD-TV, 1986 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-066)
    - Movietone News, Roaring 20s #3, undated (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-067)
    - Movietone News, Roaring 20s #4, undated (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-068)
    - Miller Genuine Draft, 2001 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-069)
    - Miller Genuine Draft: Never Miss a Genuine Opportunity, undated (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-070)
    - Nestle, undated (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-071)
    - Nestle: Butterfinger spots, 2002 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-072)
    - Nestle: Butterfinger spots, 2002 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-073)
    - Nestle: Candy bars sales video, 2003 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-074)
    - Nestle: Cookie Dough historical reel (McCann Erickson), undated (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-075)
    - Nestle: Haagen-Dazs Explainomats, 2002 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-076)
    - Nestle: Haagen-Dazs Explainomats, 2002 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-077)
    - Nestle: Signature sales video "A Day in the Life of Jean", 2003 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-078)
    - Nestle: Television spots, 2003 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-079)
    - Nestle: Tollhouse TV and Radio Historical Creative 1974-Present, 2000 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-080)
    - Nestle: Tollhouse TV on-air versions, 2004 (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-081)
    - North America Board Presentation: Training (John Furr), 1993 (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-082)
    - Northwestern Mutual Life competitive montage 5:37, 2003 (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-083)
    - New Work reel 1, undated (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-084)
      Includes Kellogg, Bristol Myers, Southland, Northwestern Mutual, Oscar Mayer, Sherwin Williams, McDonnell Douglas
    - New Work reel 2, undated (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-085)
      Includes Kellogg, Kraft, Oscar Mayer, Southland, Miller, Quaker, Bristol Myers
    - New Work reel 3, undated (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-086)
      Includes Kraft General Foods, Kellogg, Sherwin Williams
    - New Work reel 4, undated (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-087)
      Includes Kraft General Foods, Kellogg, Quaker, Oscar Mayer, Sherwin Williams, Northern Telecom
    - New Work reel 5, undated (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-088)
      Includes Kraft General Foods, Southland, Bristol Myers, Ford, Sherwin Williams, Northwestern Mutual
    - New Work reel 6, undated (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-089)
      Includes Southland, Kraft General Foods, Chuck E Cheese, Quaker, Bristol Myers, Motorola
    - New Work reel 8, undated (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-090)
      Includes Kraft, La Quinta, Nortel, Florsheim, Chuck E Cheese, Heinz, Southland, Bristol Myers, Second Harvest, Saban
    - New Work reel 9, undated (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-091)
      Includes Kraft, Heinz, Southland, Bandai, Midas, Nortel
    - New Work reel 11, undated (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-092)
      Includes Heinz, Kraft, Office Depot, Motorola, Princess Cruises, Oscar Mayer, Southland, PageNet
    - New Work reel 12, undated (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-093)
    - New Work reel 13, undated (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-094)
      Includes Kraft, Oscar Mayer, Heinz, Dell, Blockbuster
    - New Work reel 14, undated (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-095)
      Includes PDFA, Princess Cruises, Kraft, Knudsen, Blockbuster, Oscar Mayer, Claussen, Nabisco
    - New Work reel 15, undated (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-096)
      Includes Nestle, Kraft, Nabisco, Knudsen
    - New Work reel 16, undated (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-097)
      Includes Blockbuster, Miller, Oscar Mayer, Heinz, Kraft
    - New Work reel 17 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-098)
      Includes Salon Selectives, Northwestern, Blockbuster, Nabisco, Heinz, Nestle, Oscar Mayer, Louis Rich, Kraft
    - New Work reel 18, undated (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-099)
      Includes Nabisco, Helene Curtis, Kraft, VSDA, Oscar Mayer, Foster's
    - New Work reel 19, undated (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-100)
      Includes PDFA, Miller, Northwestern Mutual, Nestle, Nabisco, Salton, Foster's, Blockbuster
    - New Work reel 20, undated (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-101)
      Includes, Kraft, Nabisco, Miller, Oscar Mayer, Northwestern Mutual, Blockbuster, Nestle
    - New Work reel 21, undated (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-102)
      Includes Kraft, Salton, Nestle, Oscar Mayer, Nabisco, Western Union, PTA
    - New Work reel 22, undated (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-103)
      Includes Kraft, Northwestern Mutual, Nabisco, Oscar Mayer, Nestle, Western Union, Blockbuster, Illinois Bureau of Tourism
    - New Work reel 23, undated (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-104)
      Includes Oscar Mayer, Western Union, Stouffer's, Salton, Kraft, Nestle
    - Office Services presentation, 1993 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-105)
    - Oscar Mayer TV creative, 1995 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-106)
    - Princess Cruises sales video, 1999 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-107)
    - Princess Cruises sales video, 1999 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-108)
    - Ralph Rydholm: International advertising reel (from Information Center research reports X8.4-4-A), 1984 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-109)
    - Ralph Rydholm: Judging Creative Effectively part 1 (from Information Center research reports X8.4-3-B), 1984 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-110)
    - Ralph Rydholm: Judging Creative Effectively part 2 (from Information Center research reports X8.4-3-B), 1984 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-111)
    - Simpsons Total Branding Video, 1999 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-112)
    - Spencer Stuart H&H Full Build 06 10:15, 2001 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-113)
    - Steppenwolf Theatre TTB video, 2001 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-114)
    - Super Bowl commercials part 1, 1997 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-115)
    - Super Bowl commercials part 2, 1997 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-116)
    - Super Bowl commercials, 2002 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-117)
    - Thompson Total Branding Workshop reel, 1997 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-118)
    - Thompson Way of Planning and Creating Advertising, 1987 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-119)
    - Total Branding, 1996 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-120)
    - Total Branding, 1996 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-121)
      Includes Kodak, U.S. Marines, Motorola
    - Total Branding Cases, 1996 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-122)
      Includes Celpa, Esso, Heineken, Jaguar, Karwei, KPSM, Kellogg, Kenya Airways, Lux, Mango, Postcheque
    - Total Branding Workshop film version a, 1996 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-123)
      Includes DeBeers, Motorola, White Castle, Marine Corps, Ford, Oscar Mayer, Radio 3 Amsterdam, Nutri-Grain, Sprint
    - Total Branding Workshop film version b, 1996 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-124)
    - Tough Brand Cluster Video, undated (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-125)
    - TTB Awards Finalists, 1998 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-126)
    - TTB Case Histories "Making TTB Happen: Tape 1, 1998 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-127)
    - TTB Case Histories "Making TTB Happen: Tape 1, 1998 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-128)
    - TTB Workshop, 2001 (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-129)
    - Untitled master, undated (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-130)
    - Website studies: HeleneCurtis.com, Cheezguy.com, 2001 (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-131)
    - WRFF sales video, 2004 (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-132)
    - Compilation tape, undated (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11121-VHS-001)
      Includes Hasbro, Stouffer's, Hamburger Helper, Campbell Soup, McDonald's
    - Consumer insight presentation reel, 2000 (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11121-VHS-002)
    - Conversation with James Webb Young to be used in the speech "Ideas in the Year 2000", undated (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11121-VHS-003)
    - Day One Seducing the Muse, 1995 (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11121-VHS-004)
    - Diamond Solitaire Product Trend, undated (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11121-VHS-005)
    - Dunlop Corbin Communications: JWT Total Branding presentation, 1998 (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11121-VHS-006)
    - Einson Freeman: JWT promotional training video, 1997 (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11121-VHS-007)
    - Ford Focus press conference 30:00, undated (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11121-VHS-008)
    - Improv Mom presentation, 1998 (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11121-VHS-009)
    - JWT Chicago beer spots, undated (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11121-VHS-010)
    - Kellogg's Rome presentation, 1995 (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11121-VHS-011)
    - Kids Gender presentation, 1998 (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11121-VHS-012)
    - Nestle (JWT London), undated (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11121-VHS-013)
    - Nestle Butterfinger Trends video, 2005 (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11121-VHS-014)
    - Nestle Tollhouse Morsels Creative History 1974-1994, 1995 (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11121-VHS-015)
    - Ralph Rydholm: How to Make Client Presentations More Effective (from Information Center research reports X8.4-2-A), 1984 (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11121-VHS-016)
    - Ralph Rydholm: Judging Creative Effectively part 1 (from Information Center research reports X8.4-3-A), 1984 (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11121-VHS-017)
    - Stephen King: What Is a Brand?, 1974 (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11121-VHS-018)
    - Stouffer's reel, 2005 (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11121-VHS-019)
    - The Real Thing DSN compilation tape 1:50, 1997 (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11121-VHS-020)
    - Thompson Total Branding JWT Showreel (JWT Bangkok), undated (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11121-VHS-021)
    - Thompson Total Branding video (JWT Bangkok), undated (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11121-VHS-022)
    - Thompson Total Branding video parts 1 and 2, undated (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11121-VHS-023)
    - Western Union, 2002 (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11121-VHS-024)
    - Thompson Total Branding (JWT Bangkok), undated (Box AV9, Audio-cassette RL11121-CS-001)
    - Clio Radio Winners, 1977 (Box AV9, Audio-reel RL11121-RR-001)
    - Blockbuster Aliens and Cinderella layoff and archives, 2004 (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL11121-Bcam-001)
    - Bubble Quandary film short, undated (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL11121-Bcam-002)
    - Butterfinger sales video, 2003 (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL11121-Bcam-003)
    - Cheez Whiz Gen Y Campaign 9:10 (2000-2485) (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL11121-Bcam-004)
    - Cheryl Miller b-roll, undated (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL11121-Bcam-005)
    - Christmas layoffs and archives, 2004 (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL11121-Bcam-006)
    - Dip Dip Dip layoff and archives, 2004 (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL11121-Bcam-007)
    - Donor: Blockbuster "Introducing Dorothy Dandridge" :30, 1999 (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL11121-Bcam-008)
    - Holiday Fund Raisers, 2002 (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL11121-Bcam-009)
    - Illinois Lottery "A Day in the Life" 3:15, 2002 (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL11121-Bcam-010)
    - Illinois Lottery "Where Everybody Knows Your Game", 2002 (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL11121-Bcam-011)
    - J. Walter Thompson "Heartbeat", 2003 (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL11121-Bcam-012)
    - J. Walter Thompson "Heartbeat" logo, undated (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL11121-Bcam-013)
    - James Webb Young Awards 12:00, 2002 (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL11121-Bcam-014)
    - Kellogg's Cornflakes/Lego Vroom (JWT London), 1998 (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL11121-Bcam-015)
    - Kellogg's Frosties "Canyon" (JWT London), 1998 (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL11121-Bcam-016)
    - Kellogg's Frosties "Tiger Slam" (JWT London), undated (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL11121-Bcam-017)
    - Kellogg's Rice Krispies Eek a Mouse (JWT London), undated (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL11121-Bcam-018)
    - Kraft Color Ums, 2002 (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL11121-Bcam-019)
    - Kraft Health Archive, 2003 (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL11121-Bcam-020)
    - Kraft Kool Aid "Gimme Some of that Smile", 1999 (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL11121-Bcam-021)
    - Kraft Mayonnaise "Big Mouth", 2004 (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL11121-Bcam-022)
    - Kraft Miracle Whip Taste Challenge 2:00, 2003 (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL11121-Bcam-023)
    - Kraft Miracle Whip sales video, 2003 (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL11121-Bcam-024)
    - Kraft Oscar Mayer "So Much to Love", 2003 (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL11121-Bcam-025)
    - Kraft Shreds Archive, 2003 (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL11121-Bcam-026)
      Also Blockbuster, Oscar Mayer "So Much to Love"
    - Kraft Philly Cream Cheese "Heavenly Wake-Up", 2002 (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL11121-Bcam-027)
    - Lady Sings the Blues trailer, 2000 (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL11121-Bcam-028)
    - Liz Masakayan footage Hawaii, 1997 (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL11121-Bcam-029)
    - Losing Isaiah trailer, 2000 (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL11121-Bcam-030)
    - Miller Genuine Draft "Foley Artist", 2000 (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL11121-Bcam-031)
    - Miracle Whip sales video, 2002 (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL11121-Bcam-032)
    - Nestle Butterfinger Crisp, 2004 (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL11121-Bcam-033)
    - Nestle Butterfinger Crisp sales video, 2004 (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL11121-Bcam-034)
    - Nestle candy bars sales video, 2003 (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL11121-Bcam-035)
    - Nestle Signatures sales video "A Day in the Life of Jean", 2003 (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL11121-Bcam-036)
    - Nestle Stix spots, 2006 (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL11121-Bcam-037)
    - Nestle Tollhouse boards and archives, 2004 (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL11121-Bcam-038)
    - Nestle Wonderball Cartoon Network sales video 2:00, 2002 (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL11121-Bcam-039)
    - Northwestern Mutual Life submasters 18 spots, undated (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL11121-Bcam-040)
    - Oscar Mayer animation examples, 2004 (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL11121-Bcam-041)
    - Oscar Mayer Employee Offsite V, 2004 (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL11121-Bcam-042)
    - Oscar Mayer "Oh I Wish" layoff and archives, 2004 (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL11121-Bcam-043)
    - Oscar Mayer Talent Search, 2004 (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL11121-Bcam-044)
    - Perrigo: Cheryl Miller Back on the Court 8:06, 1997 (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL11121-Bcam-045)
    - Perrigo: Cheryl Miller Back on the Court 8:06, 1997 (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL11121-Bcam-046)
    - Perrigo: Cheryl Miller Back on the Court 8:06, 1997 (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL11121-Bcam-047)
    - PetSmart RFP agency reel and case studies, undated (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL11121-Bcam-048)
    - Philadelphia Best Foods examples, undated (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL11121-Bcam-049)
    - Philly website archive, 2002 (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL11121-Bcam-050)
    - True Crime trailer 2:55, 2000 (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL11121-Bcam-051)
    - The Wood trailer, 2000 (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL11121-Bcam-052)
    - Tim's reel archive, 2004 (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL11121-Bcam-053)
    - Today's Ritziest Toons Nabisco animation, 2004 (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL11121-Bcam-054)
    - Western Union "Behind the Scenes" 9:38, 2003 (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL11121-Bcam-055)
    - Western Union campaign archive, 2004 (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL11121-Bcam-056)
    - Western Union sales video 3:03, 2003 (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL11121-Bcam-057)
    - Western Union show reel, 2003 (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL11121-Bcam-058)
    - WRFF sales video, 2004 (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL11121-Bcam-059)
    - Butterfinger Crisp sales video, 2004 (Box AV12, Video-disc RL11121-OP-001)
    - Christmas archives and files, 2004 (Box AV12, Video-disc RL11121-OP-002)
    - Dip Dip Dip archive and work files, 2004 (Box AV12, Video-disc RL11121-OP-003)
    - Illinois Lottery additional files, undated (Box AV12, Video-disc RL11121-OP-004)
    - Illinois Lottery archive plus additional files, 2004 (Box AV12, Video-disc RL11121-OP-005)
    - Kraft Health and Wellness, undated (Box AV12, Video-disc RL11121-OP-006)
    - Kraft May Tag, 2004 (Box AV12, Video-disc RL11121-OP-007)
    - Kraft Miracle Whip sales video, 2003 (Box AV12, Video-disc RL11121-OP-008)
    - Kraft Philly Duo, 2004 (Box AV12, Video-disc RL11121-OP-009)
    - Kraft Shreds Archive, 2003 (Box AV12, Video-disc RL11121-OP-010)
    - Nabisco animation archives, 2004 (Box AV12, Video-disc RL11121-OP-011)
    - Nestle "A Day in the Life of Jean", undated (Box AV12, Video-disc RL11121-OP-012)
    - Nestle Haagen-Dazs archive plus render files, 2003 (Box AV12, Video-disc RL11121-OP-013)
    - Nestle Tollhouse boards and archives, 2004 (Box AV12, Video-disc RL11121-OP-014)
    - Nestle Treasures sales archive, 2003 (Box AV12, Video-disc RL11121-OP-015)
    - Oscar Mayer "Oh I Wish" archives, undated (Box AV12, Video-disc RL11121-OP-016)
    - PetSmart RFP and Ritz archives, undated (Box AV12, Video-disc RL11121-OP-017)
    - PetSmart RFP case studies, undated (Box AV12, Video-disc RL11121-OP-018)
    - Philadelphia Best Foods archives, 2004 (Box AV12, Video-disc RL11121-OP-019)
    - Philly website archive, 2002 (Box AV12, Video-disc RL11121-OP-020)
    - Sony: Key Insights from Total Branding Intelligence, undated (Box AV12, Video-disc RL11121-OP-021)
    - TD Movies, 2003 (Box AV12, Video-disc RL11121-OP-022)
    - Tim's reel archive, 2003 (Box AV12, Video-disc RL11121-OP-023)
    - Western Union Blowout archives and files, undated (Box AV12, Video-disc RL11121-OP-024)
    - Western Union campaign archive, undated (Box AV12, Video-disc RL11121-OP-025)
    - Western Union show reel, 2003 (Box AV12, Video-disc RL11121-OP-026)
    - Western Union show reel, 2002 (Box AV12, Video-disc RL11121-OP-027)
    - WRFF archives and files, undated (Box AV12, Video-disc RL11121-OP-028)
    - WRFF sales video, 2004 (Box AV12, Video-disc RL11121-OP-029)